The Joe Rogan experience. And by
the way, also starting in the
40s, using mercury everywhere.
The very earliest autism cases
were called Kanner Syndrome
because of a doctor who
discovered eight patients who
all had. He took care of a lot
of kids and he found this new
syndrome that he was seeing
about their behavior. They had
lost their ability to speak.
They had all kinds of problems.
And in almost every case, the
father was working with mercury,
or mercury was being used in
agriculture at that time.
Mercury was like this, you know,
this wonder problem product
because it's effing effective,
that's for sure. It does shit.
And so it was in a lot of
things. So mercury is part of a
lot of neurological injuries.
And it's, you know, go on
ChatGPT and say, should I
breathe mercury fumes? No.
Should I eat it? Touch it? No,
no, no. Should I inject it?
Pause, pause, pause. Well, in
childhood vaccines, I mean,
it's just ridiculous. I got a
quick, quick one, I want to tell
you. So I'm gonna get a lot of
shit, obviously, for this. And
what's the main criticism you
and I are both gonna get? I'm
not a doctor, I'm not a
scientist. As I mentioned, I'm a
criminologist, and I speak
English and I read very well.
And so in this book, I put
together the information that
anybody can get and put all the
citations there. But what
parents often don't know is that
this brand vaccine, vaccine
good, disease bad, there's a
ruse in there, there's a
marketing ruse, which is that if
you don't get the vaccine,
you're going to get that
disease. It is absolutely
impossible for your kid to get
all of those diseases or be
exposed to all of those
diseases. And what Humphreys
didn't talk about with you, but
she knows, is that all of the
childhood vaccine diseases, all
of them, the survival rate for a
healthy American child is 100%.
All of them, yeah. That's
inconvenient. Right. The
measles. Well, let me do measles
real quick because for 22 years,
we didn't have a single, single
measles death in the United
States for 22 years. And this is
the really. This is really
interesting math. I hope people
will take this one on board.
The death rate for vaccinated
children with measles is zero.
And the death rate for
unvaccinated children, of which
there are 9 million in America,
is zero. Meaning the
unvaccinated and the vaccinated
both have the same death rate,
zero. But people have died from
Measles? Yes, people have died
from measles. But all of these
diseases, the death rates that
are the scariest are old death
rates. Right. First of all,
measles was in descent anyway up
until as it headed into the 80s,
it was already going from, you
know, up here to down here on
the graph. Why is that? Indoor
plumbing, better nutrition.
The same thing that helped with
almost every disease here.
Texas. Texas announces second
death. But this is 2024. And
what I said was in the 22 years
before that, there had not been
a death. So what's causing these
kids to die? Well, it's. I don't
know if you've had Pierre Cory
on or other people, and I'm not.
This would be a medical question
about whether these kids died of
measles or died of poor medical
care. Died with measles? Yeah,
died with measles, et cetera.
They have other comorbidities.
Well, they had bad treatment.
It's a question for like
somebody like Pierre Cory. I'm
gonna back away from the
question, by the way. Let's own
it. Let's say, oh, they died of
measles. If that's true, then in
24 years, two kids died of
measles. You know what the death
rate is for kids from. From
tetanus, for example? The risk
is that 1 in every 154 million
Americans, children will die
from tetanus. And if you want to
make those odds better with a
vaccine, more power to you. But
1 in 154 million is pretty damn
good. And then again, very
important, what you said, that
it can be taken, the vaccine can
be taken once you have
contracted tetanus. Well, no,
once you've got the injury, you
don't have to wait if you've got
the injury. But you know this,
there's a ruse here, which is
that deep puncture wounds does
not mean tetanus. Right? Right.
You gotta search for it. And as
you'll see in this book, the
chart that shows the prevalence
of tetanus in the world is an
interesting one. But I wanna
just quickly talk about this
because I'm ready for the shit
that I'm not a doctor and I
shouldn't be saying any of this.
My view is not only should I be
saying it, but I should be doing
exactly what I've done for my
whole career, which is
investigating matters and
telling the truth. And I'm not
even, by the way, an anti
vaxxer. I think there's one
vaccine I think is a great
product, by the way. The BCG
vaccine, which is for
tuberculosis. It is used in
almost every country on Earth.
It's 100 years old. And it has
other health benefits. It helps
with other respiratory problems
and it helps with bladder
cancer. It has all kinds of
benefits. Guess what country
it's not used in? The United
States of America. That's a good
guess, Joe. The United States of
America. And why? Because the.
Can I guess. Yeah, please.
Would the patents run out? It
might be another reason. By the
way, you might be on something.
No, they would say, well, there
isn't that much tuberculosis,
but there's 9,000 cases a year
versus tetanus. Versus tetanus
with, you know, 13 cases every
10 years. I don't think most
people know that tetanus is a
bacteria. Yeah. It's not
transmissible. And many vaccines
don't stop transmission anyway,
by the way. I'm not saying they
all don't work. I'm just saying
you have to make a decision.
Imagine this. Some parents don't
want their kids to play football
because they might have a head
injury. Right? But if the
government mandated that you
play football, we'd all be
pretty pissed off. Parents
decide whether their kids can
take the bike out after sundown,
whether they can sleep over at
somebody's house. They make all
these decisions about safety,
but they give over this vaccine
decision as if it's not their
business. And, you know,
something that Bobby Kennedy is
pushing for and I think will
accomplish is called joint
decision making. And that is
that the parent and the
pediatrician will decide
together on whether or not
vaccines, when to give them,
how many, which type, et cetera.
Guess who opposes that? The
pediatricians. Right. Is that
because of financial incentives?
Holy shit. Yes. When I was a
kid, I went to the pediatrician.
Well, first of all, I went to
the doctor once. I broke my
foot. If you didn't have
vaccines and Bobby's wellness
checks and little Jamie's
wellness checks that are
necessary, that, you know, they
bring you in to get the
vaccines, pediatricians would
have to have second jobs because
most kids, particularly when
they're younger and they're not
yet affected by all the
environmental toxins, most kids
are pretty healthy. Obviously,
that's less true today than it
was when I was a kid. But I
wanna share something that I'm
itching to get out because most
people just don't know much
about vaccines. And there's
information that's all available
through CDC and fda, et cetera,
that I wanna share if you give
me permission. Sure. Okay. So
how does it start? Vaccine it
means, you know, it started from
the word cow vodka. It meant
cow. So they would take pus,
cow pus, you don't wanna waste
that stuff. And they would rub
that into wounds on people. And
then they decided, oh, maybe we
can put horse pus and cow pus
from an infected horse's hoof.
We'll rub that in. And they,
and for a long time they were
experimenting with all these
things. Some old timey vaccines
were made by. I'm gonna read it
so I get it right. Steeping them
for years in a mix of ox bile
and glycerin and potato slices.
Sounds like a joke, right? But
it's true. But science moved on
and it evolved to where vaccines
included dried rabbit spinal
cords, duck embryos, chicken
blood, human bile. Cause you
don't wanna waste that ground up
rat spleens and boiled pig skin.
So that's old time vaccines
before we knew anything about
anything. So let's switch to the
modern day vaccines because
obviously now we're real smart
and we know a lot of stuff.
Well, here is what's in your
childhood vaccines right now.
Gelatin from boiled pig skin,
kind of like the old one.
Chicken embryo protein, blood
from the hearts of cow fetuses.
DNA fragments from human
fetuses. Oil extracted from
shark livers. I mentioned
earlier, proteins from worm
ovaries, because you don't want
to leave that out. And of course
DNA fragments from monkey
kidneys. Now if that doesn't
sound like a Shakespeare play.
You know that eye of newt, toe
of frog, lizard's leg, tongue of
dog. When I hear that thing from
Macbeth, I literally can't you
just picture Gates and Offit and
Hotez sitting around in their
witches brew putting this stuff
together. I know I'm talking
fast, I'm almost done. The other
modern ingredients in childhood
vaccines, this is what you are
giving if you trust the vaccine
manufacturers. Formaldehyde, we
already know that's bad.
Polysorbate 80, which is linked
to infertility. And my absolute
favorite, potassium chloride.
Why is this my favorite?
Because that is the chemical
that is injected as the third
injection in lethal injections
by executioners. Now admittedly
infants get far less of it than
people who are executing. But we
really want to be injecting any
amount of that into human
beings. Sodium borate, Triton X,
that's what's in spermicides.
And of course until very
recently, ethylmercury. And what
is the reason why they have so
many different ingredients? So I
got it in this book, holding up
shameless plug. I got it in this
book because it's too long for
now. But they have, you can get
it from ChatGPT. They have what
I would have to call a kind of
insane reason for each of these.
Right? I mean, you just heard
what they are. I mean they're,
they're, they're nuts. And
people say, well, I'm not a
scientist. You don't realize how
very important each one of those
ingredients is. Well, I do
realize something and I don't
have to be a scientist. I don't
want mercury injected into my
kids, period. If, when I was a
kid, if a light fell and broke
on the floor, you had to call a
hazmat team to get rid of it
because it had mercury. You
can't touch it, you can't
breathe it, you can't eat it,
but you can inject it into
babies. It's actually, it's
crazy. And vaccinologists,
there's a degree of mad science
here, There's a degree of
craziness. And again, I'm still
not anti vaxx. That's not the
point. The point is learn which
products you think matter
because they're not all the
same. And what are they saying
is the reason why they have all
these different ingredients like
monkey kidneys and well, some.
Of them are, I mean, it's not.
The one that's not funny, of
course is SV40 because simian
virus 40, most people don't
know, was in the first polio
vaccine which was recalled and
then it was in the second polio
vaccine which was put out to
replace the one that had simian
virus 40. It was in that and
it's in the Pfizer COVID
vaccine, SV40 fragments. And if
you could explain how that
happened. Well, they will claim
that they were that to grow the
pathogen needs to be in some
kind of organic material and
that monkey kidneys is a good
way to do it. So simian virus 40
accidentally, they claim,
accidentally got into it. Let me
tell you what they claim for
mercury because it's a good
story too. They say that it's a
preservative and that they
needed it for multi dose vials
of the flu vaccine. Not legal in
the uk, not in Denmark, not in
Sweden, not in Switzerland, but
for some reason in the United
States it's okay until Bobby
Kennedy took it out. I mean that
committee, that Robert Malone is
on, the ACIP committee that
decides on childhood vaccines.
So why is this stuff in there?
Well, two reasons. One is that
once they get a vaccine
approved, the last thing they
want to do is come back to the
FDA and start that process all
over again to get a better
vaccine approved. Because it'll
cost billions of dollars.
Because it'll cost a lot.
Because now it will. It takes a
long time and it won't get
passed. Right. Right now the
ACIP committee. I mean, it's
happening right now. There's a
new moderna vaccine, and the
ACIP committee is saying to fda,
give me all the information on
this vaccine before we approve
it. And there is no safety, no
viable safety information on
these vaccines, particularly the
childhood vaccines. There never
was, as you learn from turtles
all the way down, never a viable
study on these. And the studies
they did would be some of them
for five days, some of them for
14 days. And I'm interested in
going a little longer than that
when it comes to my kids meaning
to know whether they had adverse
reactions. Well, they would
always quote. They always say
that there have been numerous
studies and these studies are
published. And then when RFK
pushed them on this and force
them to reveal the fact that no,
there weren't any studies that
showed it. Yeah. And there were
no. They had never done a study.
There are now three, but not
done by the government, of
comparing vaccinated kids to
unvaccinated kids for all health
outcomes. If you give a kid a
measles vaccine, it'll stop them
from getting measles for many
years. It works. But does it
also have other adverse effects?
Right. So the three studies have
been done and many, many more
problems among vaccinated kids
unrelated to the disease.
Therefore, I'm talking about
asthma and ADHD and neurological
problems and visits to the
pediatrician. It's the easiest
study in the world to do because
you go to a big company like
Kaiser, they got the kid, they
know he went in for a vaccine or
didn't, and they know how many
visits he had to the
pediatrician. And so they can
look very easily at it. It's not
a hard project to do. And that's
what Bobby and Adele Bigtree
both went done by CDC and nih.
And that's the meeting where
Fauci said, oh, yeah, I have
that study. And he did this
looking through a file box. Oh,
I can't find it. I'll send it to
you. And then they had to sue to
get it. And right before showing
up in court, they get the
letter, oh, there is no such
study. Yeah, lying. I can't say
the phrase. Lying bastards. I
can say that one, right? Yeah,
you can say whatever you want,
motherfuckers. There you go.
Thank you. That's right. Yeah.
And not just a lying
motherfucker, but a lying
motherfucker with a pardon. It
goes back to 2014. Yeah, and why
would it. Why would you even do
that? Why would you give a
doctor who saved millions of
lives from the pandemic, why
would you give him a pardon.
That goes back to 2014? Seems
insane. It seems insane that you
would even need something like
that. I'll add one more
ingredient. He wasn't charged
with anything. Right. So pardons
are typically for people who are
charged with something, not for
people who might be Sam.